Lowell Thomas Jr.
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Lowell Thomas Jr.
2.1.3.3.4
Marist College
  Box 1528
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Thomas, Jr. family, 1950 - 1960s; 4 (Box 1528)
    - Wheeling, W. Va.; Thanksgiving eve, 1950; For Sonny's lecture scrapbook, Wed. News., 1
    - Verso: Wheeling, W. Va.; Thanksgiving eve, 1950; For Sonny's lecture scrapbook, Wed. News., 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and his wife(?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and his wife(?)], 3
    - [Wife of Lowell Thomas Jr.(?)], 4
    - [Wife of Lowell Thomas Jr.(?)], 5
    - [Wife of Lowell Thomas Jr.(?)], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. on a motorbike], 7
    - [Man on a motorbike], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and his wife(?)], 9
    - Left to right: LT, Jr., his wife Tay, daughter Anne, LT, Sr., 10
    - Verso: Left to right: LT, Jr., his wife Tay, daughter Anne, LT, Sr., 10-verso
    - Left to right: LT, Jr., his wife Tay, daughter Anne, LT, Sr., 11
    - [Left to right: Son, his wife, his daughter, LT Jr.], 12
    - Verso: 7-21-64-2, 12-verso
    - [Left to right: Son, his wife, his daughter, LT Jr.], 13
    - Verso: Forty Niners in the Fifteenth[?] 7-21-64-7, 13-verso
    - [Clockwise: LT Jr., his wife, his son, his daughter, in the pool], 14
    - Verso: 7-21-64-2, 14-verso
    - [Left to right: Mrs. Lowell Thomas Jr., LT Sr., LT Jr., in a car], 15
    - [LT Jr. and others paddling a boat in the water], 16
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas Jr., shows a baby koala to his son David at the Lone Pine Sanctuary in Brisbane, Australia. Mr. Thomas recently toured the South Pacific to gather material for a series of movie illustrated travel lectures which he will present coast-to-coast in the U.S. and Canada this coming October and November. Mr. Thomas and family visited Australia, New Zealand, Tahiti, Fiji, New Caledonia, Western Samoa and American Samoa, 17
    - Note: Mr. Lowell Thomas Jr., shows a baby koala to his son David at the Lone Pine Sanctuary in Brisbane, Australia. Mr. Thomas recently toured the South Pacific to gather material for a series of movie illustrated travel lectures which he will present coast-to-coast in the U.S. and Canada this coming October and November. Mr. Thomas and family visited Australia, New Zealand, Tahiti, Fiji, New Caledonia, Western Samoa and American Samoa, 18
    - [Son holding a dog], 19
    - [LT Jr. and a woman standing in front of a plane], 20
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Thomas, Jr. family, 1959 - 1960s; 5 (Box 1528)
    - Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 1
    - Verso: Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 1-verso
    - Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 2
    - Verso: Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 2-verso
    - Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 3
    - Verso: Christmas; Hobe Sound 1959, 3-verso
    - Christmas; 1959, 4
    - Verso: Christmas; 1959, 4-verso
    - Caption: Juneau, 5
    - Caption: Juneau, 6
    - Caption: Sitka, 7
    - Caption: Petersburg, 8
    - Caption: Taken at a friend's house - October - 61, 9
    - Verso: David; 1961; Anchorage, 9-verso
    - Anne Thomas, 10
    - Verso: Anne Thomas, 10-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Thomas, Jr. family [includes color photographs], circa 1960s; 6 (Box 1528)
    - Caption: Our bedroom - green, gold and white. The kids' room's a mess!, 1
    - Caption: Our kitchen alcove with family room beyond, 2
    - Caption: Family room-fireplace will have Dutch tiles, 3
    - Caption: We caught David asleep last night with his favorite pilot cap on!, 4
    - Caption: living room, Dining end- entire wall to right is glass, gold sconces on top of cupboard will go on wall over sideboard. This is big old couch from playroom reupholstered in gold wool, 5
    - Caption: Living room (pale yellow walls), 6
    - Caption: L.T.'s walnut paneled study-little door goes to furnace + storage (kids making faces!), 7
    - Caption: L.T's study opposite end-we built in book shelves on right wall-more faces!, 8
    - [Anne and David], 9
    - [Anne and David with Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 10
    - Note: July 25; Hi! Some pictures I thought you'd like to have (have sent copies to mother, too). Perhaps Sally would like to see them - many thanks for the new Bible-quite a change! Look forward to reading it. Life hectic, as usual. Am trying to get lots done around the house while Lowell is in California. We're all well-the children swimming like fish now-also enjoying the woods and stream-haven't worn my shoes for weeks! Lots of love, Tay, 11
    - Caption: The Arctic Valley ski area, 12
    - Caption: Look what Lowell caught! Lake Nancy - June 1961, 13
    - Caption: View from living room at 10 p.m. Mt. Mckinley behind clouds. Window on right covers most of wall, 14
    - Caption: Florida - April - 1961 [From left to right: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, Tay Thomas, Jr. with her children Anne and David], 15
    - Caption: Lower level: L.T.s study - Large windows: living room; Will put lawn in her in August - also ferns and juniper against house [Tay Thomas, Jr. with children Anne and David], 16
    - Caption: The red did not reproduce well - it's a lovely "New England barn red"; Begonias [David and Anne Thomas, Jr.], 17
    - Caption: terrace will be on right - white sweet peas now cover trellis!, 18
    - Caption: July 4, 1961; From road - flowers not up yet. To come: shrubbery, window boxes, shingles, terrace; garage, 19
    - Caption: July 4th - weekend - camping in the Chugach [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 20
    - Caption: Our new "front yard" - Mts. behind clouds [Tay Thomas, Jr. with children Anne and David], 21
    - Caption: Daddy teaching the rudiments of rock climbing [Lowell Thomas, Jr. with children Anne and David], 22
    - Caption: More fishermen - Anne is an avid one - will spend several very patient hours at it [David and Anne Thomas, Jr.], 23
    - Caption: Arctic Valley ski area - January 1961, 24
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas on right], 25
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Thomas, Jr. family [color photographs], circa 1960s - 1973; 7 (Box 1528)
    - [Painting(?) of a woman in a fur coat, next to a dog], 1
    - [Painting(?) of a woman in a fur coat, next to a dog], 2
    - [Painting(?) of a woman in a fur coat, next to a dog], 3
    - Caption: Vermont - 1970, 4
    - [Left to right: LT Jr., daughter, son, wife], 5
    - [Photo of LT Jr. and family, with an attached picture on the right that says "peace on Earth"], 6
    - [LT Jr. and family at Christmas], 7
    - [LT Jr.'s son and wife at Christmas, 8
    - [LT Jr. playing a small drum kit], 9
    - [Son playing a small drum kit], 10
    - [Son and daughter playing a small drum kit and guitar], 11
    - [Family sitting down for dinner], 12
    - [Daughter sitting down at typewriter], 13
    - [Daughter playing a guitar], 14
    - Caption: Note [? ]place mats, 15
    - [Son and daughter holding a kitten], 16
    - Caption: Xmas [faded], 17
    - [Daughter's school portrait (?)], 18
    - [LT Sr. with his granddaughter at graduation], 19
    - Note: LT and Anne Thomas; Graduation - Anchorage; June 1973, 20
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Thomas, Jr. family - Christmas cards [includes color photographs], circa 1960s - 1970s; 8 (Box 1528)
    - [Christmas card 1] Caption: May the Spirit of Christmas be with you throughout the New Year [and written:] And our love, Tay + Lowell Thomas, Belated greetings due to a trip to New England Where we found more snow than in Alaska!, 1
    - [inside of christmas card 1] Caption: Dave skates on the lake behind our home, 2
    - [inside of christmas card 1] Caption: Anne competes in Junior National Cross Country race, 3
    - [Christmas card 2] Note: Peace be in thy home, And in thy heart, Or if thou roam Earth's highways wide, The Lord be at the side To bless and guide - Anonymous, 4
    - [Inside of second christmas card 2] Caption: Merry Christmas July '70; And our love, Lowell + Tay Thomas, Anne + Dave, 5
    - Note: envelope from Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s family to Mrs. Lynn Sumner in Quaker Hill, Pawling, NY, 6
    - [Cover of christmas card 3] Caption: Merry Christmas! Come look out our window, 7
    - [Inside of christmas card 3] Caption: Alaska in Summer, 8
    - [Inside of christmas card 3] Caption: Alaska in Winter, 9
    - [Back of christmas card 3] Caption: hot or cold, a warm welcome to all in our new home - Lowell + Tay Thomas, 10
    - [Christmas card 4] Caption: Daddy on the Dew Line; Mommy at the clothes line; We on the Flight line; Flying Christmas Greetings to You - Lowell, Tay, Anne and David Thomas, 11
    - Note: envelope addressed to Mrs. Lynn Sumner in Quaker Hill, Pawling, NY, 12
    - [Christmas card 5] Caption: Peace on Earth [12 copies], 13
  - Thomas, Jr. family - photographs found with Lowell Thomas, Jr.'s personal papers [includes color photographs], circa 1940s - 1980; 9 (Box 1528)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] At the Taft school, 1
    - Verso: [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] At the Taft school, 1-verso
    - LT, Jr. sitting with group of boys, likely at the Taft school, 2
    - LT, Jr. and Tay, 3
    - Verso: LT, Jr. and Tay, 3-verso
    - [LT Jr. and family with skis], 4
    - [LT Jr. and family with skis], 5
    - Barbara Britch, U.S. Junior National champ (a senior at one of our local high schools) and Anne. Barbara hopes to go to Middlebury next year. Anne wants to go to Dartmouth - she says it will be co-ed by then! The 2 Canadian girl whizzes are in the background - 15 year old twin sisters, 6
    - Verso: Barbara Britch, U.S. Junior National champ (a senior at one of our local high schools) and Anne. Barbara hopes to go to Middlebury next year. Anne wants to go to Dartmouth - she says it will be co-ed by then! The 2 Canadian girl whizzes are in the background - 15 year old twin sisters, 6-verso
    - Members of Alaska's Nordic team - 9 girls and 12 boys. Anne is standing fourth from left, 7
    - Verso: Members of Alaska's Nordic team - 9 girls and 12 boys. Anne is standing fourth from left, 7-verso
    - Anne with members of Rocky Mountain team behind her, 8
    - Verso: Anne with members of Rocky Mountain team behind her, 8-verso
    - [Anne with members of Rocky Mountain team], 9
    - Envelope that contained pictures 9.11-9.16 [Christmas, circa 1972], 10
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 11
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 12
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 13
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 14
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 15
    - [Christmas, circa 1972], 16
    - Dartmouth Winter Carnival, 1979. Dave at end of x-c [cross country] raced, with Anne and us, 17
    - Verso: Dartmouth Winter Carnival, 1979. Dave at end of x-c [cross country] raced, with Anne and us, 17-verso
    - [LT Jr. and family at daughter's wedding; opposite picture reads "peace on Earth"], 18
    - [baby photo] Mary Taylor Donoghy [Donaghy?], June 16, 1980, 19
    - Note: Mary Taylor Donoghy [Donaghy?], June 16, 1980, 20
    - [Large group of men posing for a photo], 21
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (infant photographs), 1923; 10 (Box 1528)
    - Ready for his morning swim, 6 wks., 1
    - Verso: Ready for his morning swim, 6 wks., 1-verso
    - LT, Jr. with H. G. T. [Harry G. Thomas], 2
    - Verso: LT, Jr. with H. G. T. [Harry G. Thomas], 2-verso
    - LT, Jr. with H. G. T. [Harry G. Thomas] and grandmother [Harriet Wagner Thomas], 3
    - Verso: LT, Jr. with H. G. T. [Harry G. Thomas] and grandmother [Harriet Wagner Thomas], 3-verso
    - LT, Jr. with grandmother [Harriet Wagner Thomas], 4
    - Verso: LT, Jr. with grandmother [Harriet Wagner Thomas], 4-verso
    - [LT Jr. with grandmother(?)] [3 copies], 5
    - [LT Jr. as an infant], 6
    - [LT Jr. as a toddler] [3 copies], 7
    - [LT Jr. at the beach], 8
    - [LT Jr. as an infant, sitting on the ground], 9
    - [LT Jr. as an infant], 10
    - [LT Jr. as an infant], 11
    - [LT Jr. as an infant], 12
    - [LT Jr. as an infant], 13
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (early childhood photographs), circa 1925 - early 1930s; 11 (Box 1528)
    - Junior and my dog in your mother's yard on Milwaukee [Street]; 1926 Denver, 1
    - Verso: Junior and my dog in your mother's yard on Milwaukee [Street]; 1926 Denver, 1-verso
    - [LT Jr. standing on a bench in between two men, 2
    - [hand-colored photograph], 3
    - [LT Jr. climbing around a snowy tree], 4
    - [LT Jr. climbing around a snowy tree], 5
    - Sonny March 22, 1926; Locust Farm, 6
    - Verso: Sonny March 22, 1926; Locust Farm, 6-verso
    - [Sonny March 22, 1926; Locust Farm], 7
    - [LT Jr. and two other small children playing with lambs], 8
    - [LT Jr. and another child sitting on a bench], 9
    - [LT Jr.], 10
    - [LT Jr.], 11
    - [LT Jr. and a little girl on a tricycle], 12
    - [LT Jr. playing with blocks], 13
    - [LT Jr. playing with blocks], 14
    - [LT Jr. playing with blocks], 15
    - [LT Jr. playing with a bucket in the water], 16
    - Verso: Junior 2 yrs., 16-verso
    - [LT Jr. playing around snowy trees], 17
    - [LT Jr. on skis], 18
    - [LT Jr. with a "cannon ball" wagon], 19
    - [LT Jr. painting a bench], 20
    - [LT Jr. with some flowers], 21
    - [LT Jr.], 22
    - [LT Jr. and another boy playing in a tree], 23
    - [LT Jr.], 24
    - [LT Jr., another boy, and a dog sitting on a rock], 25
    - [LT Jr., another boy, and a dog sitting on a rock], 26
    - [LT Jr. holding a toy(?) gun], 27
    - [LT Jr. holding a toy(?) gun], 28
    - [LT Jr. jumping into a lake], 29
    - [LT Jr. near a horse], 30
    - Lieut. Jack Harding, Jr. and Lowell Thomas Jr., 31
    - Lieut. Jack Harding, Jr. and Lowell Thomas Jr., 32
    - Verso: Lieut. Jack Harding, Jr. and Lowell Thomas Jr., 32-verso
    - Lieut. Jack Harding, Jr. and Lowell Thomas Jr. [2 copies], 33
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (early childhood photographs), circa 1925 - early 1930s; 12 (Box 1528)
    - Sonny and Blarney [dog] on the sled; Bobby Works and Snowball [cat], 1
    - Verso: Sonny and Blarney [dog] on the sled; Bobby Works and Snowball [cat], 1-verso
    - Making his daily rounds of the barnyard, 2
    - Verso: Making his daily rounds of the barnyard, 2-verso
    - Back in Asbury - and Mummy's boy again, 3
    - Verso: Back in Asbury - and Mummy's boy again, 3-verso
    - Sunny telling "Richards" "goo-by" as he leaves the old farm and starts for Broadway. The lady on the left is Mrs. Watkins whom he called "Wopkins." And the lady on the right is Miss Hutchison, 4
    - Verso: Sunny telling "Richards" "goo-by" as he leaves the old farm and starts for Broadway. The lady on the left is Mrs. Watkins whom he called "Wopkins." And the lady on the right is Miss Hutchison, 4-verso
    - Sonny on the farm [photograph accompanied by a letter dated 13 April 1926 from Frances Ryan Thomas to Harriet Wagner Thomas], 5
    - Verso: Sonny on the farm, 5-verso
    - Fingering his rosary and saying his prayers after punching the next door neighbor's children, 6
    - Verso: Fingering his rosary and saying his prayers after punching the next door neighbor's children, 6-verso
    - Bringing in his daily load of wood, 7
    - Verso: Bringing in his daily load of wood, 7-verso
    - Sonny and a part of his gang, 8
    - Verso: Sonny and a part of his gang, 8-verso
    - 2 years and 9 months old, 9
    - Verso: 2 years and 9 months old, 9-verso
    - Enroute from the Farm to Asbury, 10
    - Verso: Enroute from the Farm to Asbury, 10-verso
    - [LT Jr. and another man, holding fish and a fishing pole], 11
    - [LT Jr.], 12
    - [LT Jr. being held by a man], 13
    - [LT Jr. being held by a man], 14
    - [LT Jr. being held by a man], 15
    - [LT Jr. and a man, dressed nicely], 16
    - [LT Jr. sitting on the shoulders of a man], 17
    - [LT Jr. and a man sitting on a fence], 18
    - [Man smoking pipe, showng LT Jr. a gun], 19
    - [LT Jr. amongst a group of boys], 20
  Box 1529
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (youth photographs), circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1529)
    - [Boy's soccer team], 1
    - [One boy on the dock, one diving into the water], 2
    - [Boy's swimming team], 3
    - [Boy's swimming team], 4
    - [Boy's baseball team], 5
    - [Boy's baseball team], 6
    - [Three boys on horseback], 7
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 8
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 9
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 10
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 11
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 12
    - [LT Jr. with a horse], 13
    - [LT Jr. on a horse], 14
    - [LT Jr. on a tractor], 15
    - [LT Jr. on a tractor], 16
    - [LT Jr. With a young woman, holding tennis rackets], 17
    - [LT Jr. with a man, a woman and two dogs], 18
    - [LT Jr. leaning on a railing], 19
    - [LT Jr. holding freshly caught fish], 20
    - [LT Jr. and three other young adults holding caught fish], 21
    - [LT Jr. holding a cat], 22
    - [LT Jr. holding a cat], 23
    - [LT Jr. holding a cat], 24
    - [LT Jr. holding a cat], 25
    - [LT Jr. swimming], 26
    - [LT Jr. swimming], 27
    - [LT Jr. diving into a pool], 28
    - [LT Jr.], 29
    - [LT Jr. and three other young adults sitting on the front lawn of a home], 30
    - [LT Jr.(?) with a pygmy goat], 31
    - [LT Jr.(?) and another man with a pygmy goat], 32
    - [LT Jr.(?) with a pygmy goat], 33
    - [LT Jr.(?) and another man with a small puppy], 34
    - [LT Jr. posing for a photo], 35
    - [LT Jr.], 36
    - [LT Jr. and a young woman dancing], 37
    - [LT Jr. and three other young adults sitting on the ground with dogs], 38
    - [LT Jr. and three other young adults sitting on the ground with dogs], 39
    - Sonny + Pum Joes, 40
    - Verso: Sonny + Pum Joes, 40-verso
    - Sonny + Pum Joes, 41
    - Verso: Sonny + Pum Joes, 41-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (posed photographs), circa 1940s - 1950s; 2 (Box 1529)
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 1
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [27 copies], 3
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 3-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (posed photographs), circa 1940s - 1950s; 3 (Box 1529)
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 1
    - Verso: Tay, 1-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [2 copies], 2
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 3
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 4
    - [LT Jr. with a dog], [2 copies], 5
    - [LT Jr. with a dog], [2 copies], 6
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 7
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 8
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 9
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (posed photographs), circa 1940s - 1950s; 4 (Box 1529)
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 1
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [2 copies], 2
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [8 copies], 3
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 3-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 4
    - Verso: L Thomas, Jr., 4-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 5
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [4 copies], 6
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [3 copies], 7
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 7-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [11 copies], 8
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (publicity photographs), circa 1950; 5 (Box 1529)
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 1
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - posed photograph, [12 copies], 3
    - Verso: 21125-2 Neg. # at CBS Photo, 3-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (publicity photographs) [duplicates], circa 1950; 6 (Box 1529)
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - publicity photograph, [32 copies], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (in uniform), circa 1940s; 7 (Box 1529)
    - Caption: 2113ABIOMAR45 594-I Lowell Thomas JR & Students; C.A.A.F. MISS [3 copies], 1
    - Verso: Official photo of U.S. AAF by AAF Training Command, 1-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - in military uniform posing on porch, 2
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - in military uniform posing on porch, 3
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - in military uniform posing on porch, 4
    - [LT Jr. with his hat on a dog], 5
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - in military uniform posing on porch, 6
    - [LT Jr. with his hat on a dog], 7
    - [LT Jr. in front of a large cactus], 8
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - on military plane with Army Air Corps, 9
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - on military plane with Army Air Corps, 10
    - Lowell Thomas, Jr. - on military plane with Army Air Corps, 11
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 11-verso
    - [LT Jr. and two other men in front of a plane], 12
    - [LT Jr. entering a plane's cockpit], 13
    - Verso: Lodwick School of Aeronautics Photo, 13-verso
    - [LT Jr. entering a plane's cockpit], [3 copies], 14
    - [LT Jr. and another man in front of a plane], 15
    - [LT Jr.], 16
    - [LT Jr.], [5 copies], 17
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. (in uniform), circa 1940s; 8 (Box 1529)
    - [LT Jr. and three other people sitting at a dinner table], 1
    - [LT Jr. and three other people sitting at a dinner table], 2
    - [LT Jr. and numerous other men in uniform standing in a line], 3
    - Verso: If Published Please Credit to A.A.F. Classification Center, 3-verso
    - [LT Jr. and numerous other men in uniform standing in a line], 4
    - [LT Jr.], 5
    - [LT Jr.], 6
    - [LT Jr.], 7
    - [Signed picture of LT Jr.], 8
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Jr., 8-verso
    - [LT Jr.], 9
    - Verso: Lt. Lowell Thomas, 9-verso
  Box 1530
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. with grandparents, circa late 1920s; 1 (Box 1530)
    - [with Harry G. Thomas], 1
    - [with Harriet Wagner Thomas], 2
    - [with Harriet Wagner Thomas], 3
    - [with Harry P. Ryan], 4
    - [with Harry P. Ryan], 5
    - [with Harry P. Ryan], 6
    - [with Harry P. Ryan], 7
    - [with Eunice Ryan], 8
    - [with Eunice Ryan], 9
    - [with Eunice Ryan], 10
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Mary Taylor "Tay" Pryor wedding photographs, 1950 May 20; 2 (Box 1530)
    - [Mary Taylor and her father(?)], 1
    - [Mary Taylor and her father(?)], 2
    - [Mary Taylor and her father(?)], [5 copies], 3
    - [View down the altar], 4
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor walking down the aisle], [2 copies], 5
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor leaving the church], 6
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor leaving the church], 7
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor], [3 copies], 8
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor in the car], [2 copies], 9
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor in the car], 10
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor], 11
    - [The bridesmaids], 12
    - [The groomsmen], 13
    - [Family members congratulating the bride and groom], 14
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor surrounded by family and friends], 15
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor cutting the cake], 16
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor dancing], 17
    - [Left to right: LT Jr., his mother, LT Sr.], 18
    - [The bride with her in-laws], 19
    - [Mary Taylor, her mother and her father], 20
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Mary Taylor "Tay" Pryor wedding photographs [proofs], 1950 May 20; 3 (Box 1530)
    - Note: May 20, 1950, Pryor-Thomas, Proof Photos, Will Fade, 1
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor in the car], 2
    - [LT Jr. and Mary Taylor in the car], 3
    - [Mary Taylor getting into the car], 4
    - [Overview of the church], 5
    - [Overview of the church], 6
    - [Overview of the church], 7
    - [Some bridesmaids], 8
    - [A bridesmaid looking in the mirror], 9
    - [LT Jr. and Sr. talking with clergymen], 10
    - [LT Sr. with clergymen], 11
    - [LT Jr. with his mother and father], 12
    - [The groomsmen], 13
    - [Family and friends], 14
    - [LT Sr. and his wife with Mary Taylor's parents], 15
    - [LT Sr. and a bridesmaid], 16
    - [LT Sr. and a bridesmaid], 17